= kisskh.lv =
SAY NO TO PIRACY, SUPPORT ORIGINALS
ADAPTED FROM THE EARLY SPRING ON JJWXC.NET
AUTHOR: GU NIANG BIE KU
TREAT EVERY DAY SERIOUSLY
EVERY DAY WILL BE BETTER
GOT BACK TO CLIENT ON BUDGET TODAY
FOLLOW UP ON DESIGN DRAFT
UPDATE PLANNING DIVISION
CLIENT POSTPONES PRESENTATION TO MONDAY
COMPILE TIANYUE PROJECT SUMMARY REPORT
REPORT LACKS: 1. COMPETITIVE ANALYSIS
2. CHANGE IN MARKET SHARE
3. DATA SUPPORT
4. RISK ASSESSMENT
WORKPLACE VIBE IMPROVEMENT PLAN
SPEECH HABITS, BODY LANGUAGE
MENTALITY ADJUSTMENT
COMMUNICATION SKILLS
TODAY'S OBSERVATION, LEARNING PLAN
CAN YOU CONTROL THE FEELING OF LOVE?
I got this from saving you.
In ancient times, you'd have to…
Marry me.
Shang Zhitao.
Your eyebrows. Why do you always frown?
Are you tired?
Come home with me.
What's going on?
Come on. Give it to me.
Nothing. It's…
I sprained my ankle.
Is it serious?
- Do you need to go to the hospital?
- It's not.
It's fine. No need to go to the hospital.
What happened?
Today
isn't my day.
The event was ruined.
One of our customers
already has a boyfriend,
but she still joined our event.
In the end,
her boyfriend came to the venue
and made a mess out of it.
I wanted to say something to comfort her,
but she pushed me down on the ground.
I sprained my ankle, and it hurts.
Don't catch a cold.
Go back first.
Let's go.
- Did I get it dirty?
- It's fine. Slow down.
Give me a hand.
Come.
Come inside.
Fish.
Come here.
Hello?
Where are you?
We are going to the next place now.
We want to keep drinking at your home.
Luan Nian, we are going to your home.
We are going to keep celebrating!
Don't come.
Go back to your own homes.
I don't welcome anyone.
SUN YUANZHU
She's still not answering?
Luan Nian?
Luke.
Where am I?
This is my house.
Thank you.
You were drunk
and couldn't say your address clearly.
I had to bring you here
and wait for you to sober up
before sending you home.
Sorry for troubling you.
Did I embarrass myself
when I was drunk?
You did.
You spouted nonsense and confessed to me.
You wanted me to marry you.
Don't… Don't believe anything I said.
They say the words you say
when you're drunk are all nonsense.
When I am sober,
I've never thought about this.
Are you single?
Yes.
Why don't we give it a try?
No…
There's no need.
When it comes to thoughts
that I shouldn't be having,
I can control them really well.
Can you control the feeling of love?
I'm going to the toilet.
Are you going to my room?
The toilet is on the right.
Get changed.
You'll feel more comfortable.
Thank you.
LONG ZHENTIAN
Zhentian. Are you guys still outside?
I went home.
Shang Zhitao met someone called Luke
at the bar a few hours ago.
He asked her to work overtime.
Work overtime?
Yes. It was very unreasonable,
but Flora agreed.
All right. Rest early.
We're in the same boat.
Let me dress the wound for you.
I've been dreaming about you lately.
In ancient times, you'd have to…
Marry me.
Have you finally realized?
You can't control the feeling of love.
Your phone has been ringing all night.
Answer it.
- Hi, Sun Yu.
- Tao.
You scared me.
Sun Yuanzhu and I
almost called the police.
Where are you? We'll go pick you up.
No need.
I can go back on my own.
I'll take you home later.
Why do I hear a man's voice?
Tao, are you safe?
You must be safe.
If you are in danger,
- I'm safe.
- tap the phone.
I'm very safe.
Long Zhentian said a man called Luke
took you away when you were at the bar.
Is Luke Luan Nian?
It's him.
Got it.
The rain is heavy outside.
It'll be hard to get a taxi.
If you're coming back tomorrow,
remember to stay safe
and protect yourself.
All right. I'm hanging up.
Are you going back?
It's raining outside.
You can't get a taxi easily.
I drank, so I can't drive.
Besides, your friend said
it'd be troublesome
to get a taxi when it was raining.
You can go back tomorrow.
Sure.
Shang Zhitao,
are you sober now?
Do you know what will happen next?
Thanks for last night.
Welcome to the weather forecast.
Today is April 12th, 2013.
Beijing is cloudy, but turning clear.
The temperature is around
23 degrees Celsius.
Last night's storm brought
a good amount of nutrients to plants.
There's sufficient sunlight today
with average humidity levels.
LUAN NIAN: IT'S NOTHING MUCH
Hello.
Is she from 2501?
It's none of your business.
Get back in your position.
Today's weather sure is nice.
The sun is shining brightly.
Yes.
How can the morning sun
be so pretty?
Great.
You're giving me the silent treatment.
You're a jerk.
Why did you leave in a rush yesterday?
You didn't even take your jacket
or drive your car.
I had to deliver them to you.
You're back.
You're quite open-minded, Shang Zhitao.
It was an accident.
I know it was an accident for you.
What about Luan Nian?
Was it the same for him?
I guess it counts as an accident.
That's great.
Men and women in this city
have happy accidents every day.
It's a good thing.
My hunch is always accurate.
When you first
brought that girl to my place,
I knew there would be a spark
between you two.
You must have been planning this
for a long time.
He first saved your life
and then created an accident.
In my opinion,
he has been advancing step by step
for a long time.
Don't make it sound like he's a jerk.
I still respect him a lot.
Respect? What kind of respect?
Bowing to him on the bed?
Enough…
I have no interest in spending time
and energy to date someone.
You don't date people, indeed.
Girls are the ones
throwing themselves at you.
She's really not the type
to throw herself at someone.
Then you've got to tell me about that.
So, what kind of person is she?
Even among us,
people can be very different.
The ideas he comes up with in 0.1 seconds
can satisfy the clients.
He is talented
and has become an expert in this industry
at such a young age.
Any ordinary person
will need ten years, at least,
to reach his position.
I get it now.
Men who are outstanding at work
are indeed charming.
What about his life?
How is his private life?
I think he's a bit lonely.
Shang Zhitao, you're done for.
When you unknowingly feel sorry for a man,
it's the beginning
of falling wholeheartedly in love.
I really think Ms. Shang
is different from all those girls
who fawned over you
and flattered you in the past.
She seems kind and pure.
If you two are meant for each other,
don't stick to your outdated beliefs.
Let go of your past prejudices
and try dating her.
That's your prejudice against me.
In your opinion, am I evil or am I a jerk?
I wish you were a jerk.
You need to know your true self.
You are just an arrogant, silly,
and oblivious guy.
Once a girl starts clinging to you,
you immediately turn into
a heartless man who needs no love.
Listen to me.
Love at first sight
or love that never fades
doesn't exist in this world.
Wake up.
Get lost.
Fine. I still have something to do
at my restaurant.
I won't disturb you anymore.
I'm leaving.
Whose… Whose bag is this?
Just leave it there.
Ms. Shang purposely left it here.
She's playing hard to get.
Take your chance when you need to.
Go for it.
I'm leaving.
LUAN NIAN
Answer it. Answer it.
It's Luke.
Where are you?
I'm home.
I'll come find you tonight.
Sure.
What did he say?
He said
he'd come find me tonight.
He's going to confess.
I don't think so.
Regardless, you must
put on full makeup tonight.
Even if you're just taking a stroll,
you must look pretty.
Go. Get changed.
Hurry up.
Stop wasting time.
You've put on makeup.
Why did you ask to meet up?
Are you sober now?
You left your bag at my place.
I forgot.
Thanks.
Sorry.
I made you come all the way here
to return my bag.
Ms. Shang purposely left it here.
She's playing hard to get.
You purposely left your bag at my place
so I'd come and find you.
It wasn't on purpose.
Are you worried that I'd cling to you?
Don't worry.
Last night was just an accident
between two adults.
Thank you again for coming here
to return my bag.
I'm going back.
You purposely left your bag at my place
so I'd come and find you.
Why… Why are you back so soon?
What happened?
I left my bag at his place.
He came to return it.
And he told me
not to get the wrong idea.
What a jerk.
I…
What's done is done.
Stop thinking about it.
People make rash decisions all the time.
He takes advantage of his good looks,
so he sees women as his prey.
Just stay away from him in the future.
Look at me.
Do you know
the three golden rules of modern love?
Don't ask about the past.
Don't gamble on the future.
Cherish the present.
I overestimated myself.
He and I are not from the same world.
I still fell for it.
I didn't want to hear it from him,
so I said it was an accident yesterday.
When it comes to love,
no one is right or wrong.
You think he's experienced,
but he might have gotten hurt once
by a woman as well.
Probably.
I'm just a passerby in his love life.
Tao, cheer up.
Love isn't the only thing in life.
I'll attend English lessons
starting tomorrow.
I'm going to study and improve.
That's right.
Improve and study whenever you can.
Focus on yourself.
Don't let love sidetrack your ambition.
I'm counting on you
to support me in the future.
That's right. I want bread
for tomorrow morning.
Bring some back after class.
To repay you, I can introduce you
to some of our finest clients.
Pick anyone you want.
I don't need you to repay the favor.
Of course I'll bring you bread.
Sure.
Bread is indeed…
more important than love.
You really are a silly and oblivious guy.
I was just saying,
and you actually went and asked her.
Hurry and go make it up to her.
This bag I just sent you
is a limited-edition design.
However, it's already
reserved for a customer.
If you like it, I'll order it for you.
I want this one.
I want it today.
Mr. Luan, this won't do.
This one is for another customer.
For this one, we need to allocate stock
before we can get it from another store.
Do what you must.
If I can get it by today,
I'll buy out your shop's watches,
belts, and cutlery.
I'll come pick them up later.
Sure. I'll think of something.
I'll get everything ready for you
and have someone deliver them to your car.
THE NEXT TRAIN ARRIVES IN ONE MINUTE
It means you gain wisdom
through experience.
SUN YU: DON'T FORGET TO BUY BREAD
Mr. Long, let's end the lesson here.
I still have something to do.
- Let me pay the bill.
- No.
It's my treat today.
You taught me English today.
Let me pay today.
In the next lesson, you can tell me
more about Chinese allusions
to pay me back.
Sure. In the next lesson, I'll tell you
a story about reciprocity
and returning kindness.
I only know the phrase,
"Don't bite the hand that feeds you."
You know quite a lot.
It's nothing much.
HAPPINESS PASTRY
BLACK TRUFFLE MUSHROOM BEEF PUFF
30.6 YUAN
CHEESY CHICKEN BUN, 30.6 YUAN
BIRTHDAY PARTY HAT
Why are they so expensive?
HALF PRICE AT 9 P.M. EVERY NIGHT
SUN YU
Sun Yu.
The bread here is half price after nine.
What do you want? I'll buy them for you.
Sure.
LUAN NIAN: ARE YOU STILL AT HOME?
They say the heart is a narrow door.
Once you get hurt,
it'll leave a crack that gets in the way.
When your sincerity
is being taken lightly,
it's worse than getting hurt physically.
The soft thorn deep in my heart,
once touched, brings embarrassment.
Just thinking about it
makes me feel disheartened.
Dear customers,
our freshly baked bread
will be sold at half price soon.
If you are interested,
please proceed to the bread area.
HAPPINESS PASTRY
Luke?
Why are you here?
Can I help you?
It's for you.
I don't need this.
That bag of yours is too old.
Use a new one.
This bag is good enough.
I don't need to change it.
Don't worry.
What happened two days ago
was an accident.
You're afraid of being pestered.
And I'm also quite busy.
Is that what you think?
There's nothing more to it.
Don't worry.
I'm a pragmatist.
Between work and love,
I'll surely choose work.
In the future,
let's just…
forget this ever happened.
Let's just be strangers.
You care a lot about this job.
Of course.
I hope this incident
won't affect your opinion of my work.
It won't.
That's good to hear.
You may go back.
This bag is too expensive.
It's not suitable for me.
So even without accepting the bag,
you still want to date me?
We are…
not in an official relationship.
Tao…
What is an official relationship
in this day and age?
A sincere promise or a fake confession?
Love is always complicated.
Even if it's planned,
it's not necessarily fake.
Even if you're discussing marriage,
it might still not be true love.
He is my boss.
When I joined the company,
he asked me to quit on my first day.
I was very nervous back then.
I felt that he wasn't joking
when he said that.
Did you offend him?
Then I'm sure he is interested in you.
I don't think so.
He doesn't seem like someone
who lacks girlfriends.
In his eyes, I'm probably
a person made up entirely of flaws.
I should probably focus
on how to survive in Lime.